var questionSet = [{
  question: "What was the first movie released in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
  answer: "Iron Man",
  choicesArray: ["Incredible Hulk", "Captain America", "Spiderman", "Iron Man"]
}, {
  question: "Which character in Toy Story was voiced by Tom Hanks?",
  answer: "Woody",
  choicesArray: ["Buzz Lightyear", "Mr. Potato Head", "Woody", "Slinky"]
}, {
  question: "Who starred as a genius character in Good Will Hunting?",
  answer: "Matt Damon",
  choicesArray: ["Matt Damon", "Ben Affleck", "Robin Williams", "Kevin Costner"]
}, {
  question: "Which movie was also directed by the director of The Dark Knight?",
  answer: "Memento",
  choicesArray: ["Donnie Darko", "Memento", "The Illusionist", "Gravity"]
}, {
  question:"Famous singer Madonna made a cameo in which James Bond film?",
  answer: "Die Another Day",
  choicesArray: ["Die Another Day", "Tomorrow Never Dies", "Licence to Kill", "The World is Not Enough"]
}, {
  question: "The director of Reservoir Dogs also appeared in it as which character?",
  answer: "Mr. Brown",
  choicesArray: ["Mr. Orange", "Mr. Brown", "Mr. Pink", "Mr. Blue"] 
}, {
  question: "Which movie was not based on a true story",
  answer: "Sicario",
  choicesArray: ["Spotlight", "American Hustle", "Zodiac", "Sicario"]
}, {
  question: "Which actor was originally offered the role of main character in Elysium?",
  answer: "Eminem",
  choicesArray: ["Eminem", "Leonardo Dicaprio", "Adrien Brody", "Keanu Reeves"]
}, {
  question: "Which one is the first James Bond film to be produced?",
  answer: "Dr. No",
  choicesArray: ["Goldfinger", "From Russia with Love", "Dr. No", "You Only Live Twice"]
}, { 
  question:"Bill Murray has not appeared in which of these films?",
  answer: "Spy",
  choicesArray: ["Get Smart", "Spy", "Zombieland", "The Darjeeling Limited"]
}, {
  question: "Which actor has not been in a Star Wars movie?",
  answer: "Rainn Wilson",
  choicesArray: ["Daniel Craig", "Rainn Wilson", "Joel Edgerton", "Warwick Davis"]
}, {
  question: "Who plays a small role in Hot Fuzz as the ex-girlfriend of Simon Pegg's character?",
  answer: "Cate Blanchett",
  choicesArray: ["Rebecca Ferguson", "Olivia Colman", "Keira Knightley", "Cate Blanchett"]
}];